Guide to the Arlen Specter Senatorial Papers, Group 2. Legislative Files, 1965-2011 TJU.2010.01.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Research Files, 1967-2010; II.
  - Economic Issues, 1980-2009; 4.
    - Tax, Earned income tax credit, 1995-1996 (Box 229, Folder 13)
    - Tax, Election worker Social Security tax exclusion, 1992 (Box 229, Folder 14)
    - Tax, Electronic federal tax payment system, 1996 (Box 229, Folder 15)
    - Tax, Employer Provided Education Assistance Act, 1997 (Box 229, Folder 16)
    - Tax, Energy tax, 1993 (Box 229, Folder 17)
    - Tax, Estate tax exemption, 1993 (Box 229, Folder 18)
    - Tax, Estate tax reforms, 1996 (Box 229, Folder 19)
    - Tax, Export Source Coalition, 1997 (Box 229, Folder 20)
    - Tax, Extensions, 1991-1992 (Box 229, Folder 21)
    - Tax, Family Heritage Preservation Act, 1997 (Box 229, Folder 22)
    - Tax, Federal Insurance Contributions Act (FICA), Payroll taxes and employee tips, 1992-1993 (Box 229, Folder 23)
    - Tax, Federal tax issues, 1989 (Box 229, Folder 24)
    - Tax, Finance and tax summary, 1995 (Box 229, Folder 25)
    - Tax, Flat tax, 1995 (Box 229, Folder 26-30)
    - Tax, Flat tax draft, 1995 (Box 230, Folder 1)
    - Tax, Foreign owned firm taxation, 1990 (Box 230, Folder 2)
    - Tax, General background, Roth, 1997 (Box 230, Folder 3)
    - Tax, Letters to Finance Committee, 1997 (Box 230, Folder 4)
    - Tax, Luxury excise tax, 1992 (Box 230, Folder 5)
    - Tax, Luxury tax and fur industry, 1993 (Box 230, Folder 6)
    - Tax, Gas tax, 1996 (Box 230, Folder 7)
    - Tax, Gas tax repeal, 1996 (Box 230, Folder 8)
    - Tax, Health insurance 25% deduction, 1995 (Box 230, Folder 9)
    - Tax, Historic Homeownership Assistance Act, 1997 (Box 230, Folder 10)
    - Tax, Home-Based Business Fairness Ac, 1997 (Box 230, Folder 11)
    - Tax, Home Office Deduction Act, 1995 (Box 230, Folder 12)
    - Tax, Independent Contractor Tax Simplification Act, 1996 (Box 230, Folder 13)
    - Tax, IRA, Adoption, 1997 (Box 230, Folder 14)
    - Tax, IRA, Withdrawal proposal, 1992 (Box 230, Folder 15)
    - Tax, IRS, Amish letter, 1996 (Box 230, Folder 16)
    - Tax, IRS, Budget cuts, 1984-1986 (Box 230, Folder 17)
    - Tax, IRS, Computer studies, 1980-1985 (Box 230, Folder 18)
    - Tax, IRS, Correspondence, 1986 (Box 230, Folder 19)
    - Tax, IRS, GAO briefings and reports, 1985 (Box 230, Folder 20)
    - Tax, IRS, Hearings and testimonies, 1985 (Box 230, Folder 21-26)
    - Tax, IRS, Hearings and testimonies, 1985 (Box 231, Folder 1)
    - Tax, IRS, Income tax general information, 1996-1997 (Box 231, Folder 2-3)
    - Tax, IRS, Information, 1994 (Box 231, Folder 4)
    - Tax, IRS, Legislation, 1985 (Box 231, Folder 5)
    - Tax, IRS, Newsclips, 1985 (Box 231, Folder 6)
    - Tax, IRS, Philadelphia Service Center downsizing investigation, 1992-1993 (Box 231, Folder 7)
    - Tax, IRS, Philadelphia Service Center inquiry newsclips, 1985 (Box 231, Folder 8)
    - Tax, Internet tax, 2003 (Box 231, Folder 9)
    - Tax, Letters to Pennsylvania CEOs, 1989-1990 (Box 231, Folder 10)
    - Tax, Low income housing credit, Mortgage revenue bond program, 1994 (Box 231, Folder 11)
    - Tax, Minority and Women Capital Formation Act, 1992 (Box 231, Folder 12)
    - Tax, Minority and Women Capital Formation Act, 1996 (Box 231, Folder 13)
    - Tax, Mortgage revenue bonds, 1986-1993 (Box 231, Folder 14)
    - Tax, Net operating losses, 1997 (Box 231, Folder 15)
    - Tax, New Urban Agenda tax issues, 1995 (Box 231, Folder 16)
    - Tax, Old Order Amish, 1996 (Box 231, Folder 17)
    - Tax, Orphan drug tax credit, 1997 (Box 231, Folder 18)
    - Tax, Passive loss rules, 1991 (Box 231, Folder 19)
    - Tax, Payroll tax, 1995 (Box 231, Folder 20)
    - Tax, Peace tax fund, 1996 (Box 231, Folder 21)
    - Tax, Pennsylvania Farm Bureau, 1995 (Box 231, Folder 22)
    - Tax, Pennsylvania tax reform, 1993 (Box 231, Folder 23-24)
    - Tax, Pension fund taxation, 1992-1995 (Box 231, Folder 25)
    - Tax, Possessions tax credit, 1996 (Box 231, Folder 26)
    - Tax, Prepaid tuition plans, 1995 (Box 231, Folder 27)
    - Tax, Property and casualty insurance, 1993 (Box 231, Folder 28)
    - Tax, Puralube oil tax amendment, 1996 (Box 231, Folder 29)
    - Tax, Real estate tax provisions, 1993 (Box 231, Folder 30)
    - Tax, Reform, 1984-1985 (Box 231, Folder 31)
    - Tax, Reform, 1995 (Box 231, Folder 32)
    - Tax, R&D tax credit extension, 1997 (Box 232, Folder 1)
    - Tax, Retirement Equity Act and Economic Equity Act, 1983 (Box 232, Folder 2-4)
    - Tax, Revenue estimates, 1993 (Box 232, Folder 5)
    - Tax, Savings and Investment Incentive Act, 1997 (Box 232, Folder 6)
    - Tax, Section 89 repeal, 1989 (Box 232, Folder 7)
    - Tax, Senator Breaux child tax credit, 1995 (Box 232, Folder 8)
    - Tax, Small Business Tax Act, 1996 (Box 232, Folder 9)
    - Tax, Small issue industrial development bonds, 1991 (Box 232, Folder 10)
    - Tax, Software Export Equity Act, 1997 (Box 232, Folder 11)
    - Tax, Source tax elimination (Box 232, Folder 12)
    - Tax, Specter/Domenici IRA Bill, 1992 (Box 232, Folder 13)
    - Tax, Specter letters, 1995 (Box 232, Folder 14)
    - Tax, Stop Tax Exempt Arena Debt Issuance Act, 1996-1997 (Box 232, Folder 15)
    - Tax, Supermajority, 1995 (Box 232, Folder 16)
    - Tax, Tax Bill, 1992 (Box 232, Folder 17)
    - Tax, Tax Bill, Amendment on tobacco advertising, 1992 (Box 232, Folder 18)
    - Tax, Tax Bill, Amendment on non-conventional energy production from coal, 1992 (Box 232, Folder 19)
    - Tax, Tax Bill, Correspondence to administration, 1991 (Box 232, Folder 20)
    - Tax, Tax Bill, Estimated revenue effects, 1992 (Box 232, Folder 21)
    - Tax, Tax Bill, IRA, 1992 (Box 232, Folder 22)
    - Tax, Tax Bill, Memos, 1992 (Box 232, Folder 23)
    - Tax, Tax components, 1991 (Box 232, Folder 24)
    - Tax, Tax cut proposals, 1994 (Box 232, Folder 25)
    - Tax, Tax foundation reports, 1996 (Box 232, Folder 26)
    - Tax, Tax Reform Act of 1986 Section 1706 modification, 1993 (Box 232, Folder 27)
    - Tax, Tax reform proposal meeting, 1994 (Box 232, Folder 28)
    - Tax, Tax Section 1706 repeal, 1995 (Box 232, Folder 29)
    - Tax, Taxpayer Bill of Rights, 1996 (Box 232, Folder 30)
    - Tax, Taxpayer Browsing Protection Act, 1997 (Box 232, Folder 31)
    - Tax, Taxpayer Refund Act, 1999 (Box 232, Folder 32-33)
    - Tax, Taxpayer Refund Act, 1999 (Box 233, Folder 1)
    - Tax, Taxpayer Relief Act, 1997 (Box 233, Folder 2-3)
    - Tax, Technical corrections to tax bills, 1994 (Box 233, Folder 4-5)
    - Tax, Three Gorges Dam project, China, 1995 (Box 233, Folder 6)
    - Tax, Trade development legislation and appropriations, 1995 (Box 233, Folder 7-8)
    - Tax, Urban incentives, 1994-1995 (Box 233, Folder 9)
    - Tax, Venture capital and alternative minimum tax, 1995 (Box 233, Folder 10)
    - Tax, Votes, 104th Congress, 1st session, 1995 (Box 233, Folder 11)
    - Tax, Votes, 105th Congress, 1st session, 1997 (Box 233, Folder 12)
    - Tax, Votes, 105th Congress, 2nd session, 1998 (Box 233, Folder 13)
    - Tax, Votes, 106th Congress, 1st session, 1999 (Box 233, Folder 14)
    - Tax, Votes, 106th Congress, 2nd session, 2000 (Box 233, Folder 15)
    - Tax, Votes, 107th Congress, 1st session, 2001 (Box 233, Folder 16)
    - Tax, Votes, 107th Congress, 2nd session, 2002 (Box 233, Folder 17)
    - Tax, Westinghouse pension, Excise tax issue, 1996 (Box 233, Folder 18)
    - Tax, Women's Investment and Savings Equity Act, 1997 (Box 233, Folder 19)
    - Teamsters business and banking issues, 1993 (Box 233, Folder 20)
    - Trade associations, 1984 (Box 233, Folder 21)
    - Trade Bill, Unfair Foreign Competition Act, 1987 (Box 233, Folder 22-23)
    - Trade Bill, Unfair Foreign Competition Act, 1987 (Box 234, Folder 1-8)
    - Trade Bill, Unfair Foreign Competition Act, Actions and proposals, 1985-1988 (Box 234, Folder 9-12)
    - Trade Bill, Unfair Foreign Competition Act, Amendments, 1987 (Box 234, Folder 13-14)
    - Trade Bill, Unfair Foreign Competition Act, Amendments, 1987 (Box 235, Folder 1-2)
    - Trade Bill, Unfair Foreign Competition Act, Customs statutes and background, 1987 (Box 235, Folder 3-6)
    - Trade Bill, Unfair Foreign Competition Act, Reference materials, 1985-1988 (Box 235, Folder 7-10)
    - Trade, China and tungsten market issues, 1992 (Box 235, Folder 11)
    - Trade, China IPR sanctions, 1996 (Box 235, Folder 12)
    - Trade, China Most-Favored Nation (MFN), 1992 (Box 235, Folder 13)
    - Trade, China MFN, 1994 (Box 235, Folder 14)
    - Trade, Coal and coke, 2001 (Box 235, Folder 15)
    - Trade, Commodity control list, 1993 (Box 235, Folder 16)
    - Trade, Commodity Trading Fixtures Commission, 1982 (Box 235, Folder 17)
    - Trade, Correspondence and memos, 1990-1995 (Box 235, Folder 18)
    - Trade, Customs fraud, 1983 (Box 236, Folder 1)
    - Trade, Emergency Committee for American Trade, 1993 (Box 236, Folder 2)
    - Trade, Export conference, 1982 (Box 236, Folder 3-4)
    - Trade, Foreign Corrupt Packages Act amendments, 1980-1981 (Box 236, Folder 5)
    - Trade, Heavyweight motorcycles, 1982-1983 (Box 236, Folder 6-7)
    - Trade, Inverted tariff legislation, 1991-1992 (Box 236, Folder 8)
    - Trade, Machine tool voluntary restraint agreements, 1991-1992 (Box 236, Folder 9)
    - Trade, Rope and cordage imports, 1983 (Box 236, Folder 10)
    - Trade, Sanyo Audio tariff issue, 1991-1992 (Box 236, Folder 11)
    - Trade, Senate Steel Caucus, 1994-1996 (Box 236, Folder 12-16)
    - Trade, Senate Steel Caucus, 1999-2003 (Box 236, Folder 17)
    - Trade, Senate Steel Caucus discussion, 1994 (Box 236, Folder 18)
    - Trade, Soybean resolution, 1991 (Box 236, Folder 19)
    - Trade, State of US steel industry, 1984 (Box 236, Folder 20-21)
    - Trade, Steel, 1982 (Box 237, Folder 1)
    - Trade, Steel, 1999-2001 (Box 237, Folder 2-6)
    - Trade, Tied aid credits, 1992 (Box 237, Folder 7)
    - Trade, Trade adjustment assistance, 1991-1994 (Box 237, Folder 8)
    - Trade, Trade Bill data banks and exporters, 1982-1983 (Box 237, Folder 9-10)
    - Trade, Trade Expansion and Enforcement Act, 1992 (Box 237, Folder 11)
    - Trade, Trade information, 2001 (Box 237, Folder 12)
    - Trade, Trade issues, 1985-1987 (Box 237, Folder 13)
    - Trade, Trade statement, 1992 (Box 237, Folder 14)
    - US Chamber of Commerce, 1995 (Box 237, Folder 15)
    - US Chamber of Commerce, Spirit of Enterprise Award presentation, 1996 (Box 237, Folder 16)
  - Education, 1981-2009; 5.
    The Education subseries includes material on primary and secondary education, Pennsylvania programs, and other related topics.
    - Accuracy in Campus Crime Reporting Act, 1998 (Box 238, Folder 1-5)
    - Albert Career School, 2009 (Box 238, Folder 6)
    - Ben-Gurion University of the Negev, Irvin Borowsky tribute, 1997 (Box 238, Folder 7)
    - Bilingual education impact aid, 1985 (Box 238, Folder 8)
    - Bloomsburg University, 2009 (Box 238, Folder 9)
    - Camphill Special School, Funding and information, 2006-2009 (Box 238, Folder 10)
    - Collegiate Housing and Infrastructure Act, 2009 (Box 238, Folder 11)
    - Communities in schools, 2008-2009 (Box 238, Folder 12)
    - Early Care and Education Consortium, 2009 (Box 238, Folder 13)
    - Education Daily, 1986 (Box 238, Folder 14)
    - Education Management Corporation, Stafford Loans, 2009 (Box 238, Folder 15)
    - Educational outreach, 1990 (Box 238, Folder 16)
    - Educational research centers, 1981 (Box 238, Folder 17)
    - Elwyn Education Division, 2007-2009 (Box 238, Folder 18)
    - English as a second language (ESL), Foreign language education, 2007-2009 (Box 238, Folder 19)
    - Financial aid programs, 1982-1983 (Box 238, Folder 20)
    - Financial aid, Scholarship information for undergraduate students, 1985 (Box 238, Folder 21)
    - Government role in higher education, 1986 (Box 238, Folder 22)
    - Hahnemann University Ambulatory Care and Teaching Center, 1993 (Box 238, Folder 23)
    - High school dropout rates, 1985 (Box 238, Folder 24)
    - Higher education, 1994-1998 (Box 238, Folder 25-26)
    - Jacob J. Javits Gifted and Talented Education Act, 1985 (Box 238, Folder 27)
    - Library Services and Technology Act, 2008-2009 (Box 238, Folder 28)
    - Mercyhurst College Intelligence Studies Program, 2009 (Box 238, Folder 29)
    - Middle level reform and success, 2006-2009 (Box 238, Folder 30)
    - National Alliance for Public Charter Schools, 2009 (Box 238, Folder 31)
    - National Association for Sport and Physical Education physical activity guidelines, 2008 (Box 238, Folder 32)
    - National Association of Music Merchants, Music education, 2009 (Box 238, Folder 33)
    - National Association of Private Special Education Centers, 2009 (Box 238, Folder 34)
    - National School Lunch Program, 1983 (Box 238, Folder 35)
    - Nursing education, 1984 (Box 238, Folder 36)
    - Penn State, Government programs, 1992 (Box 238, Folder 37)
    - Pennsylvania Afterschool Youth Development Network, 2009 (Box 238, Folder 38)
    - Pennsylvania School Board Delegation Luncheon, 1986 (Box 238, Folder 39)
    - Pennsylvania State Education Association, 1986 (Box 238, Folder 40)
    - Philadelphia Higher Education Agency, 1985 (Box 239, Folder 1)
    - Philadelphia Wireless Technical Institute, 1995-1997 (Box 239, Folder 2)
    - Pittston Memorial Library, 2009 (Box 239, Folder 3)
    - Propel Schools, 2008-2009 (Box 239, Folder 4)
    - School choice, 1992-1993 (Box 239, Folder 5)
    - Senator Hollings Education Amendment, 1983 (Box 239, Folder 6)
    - Statistics on incarceration and the "Cradle to College" Model, 2009 (Box 239, Folder 7)
    - Tax-exempt status of private schools, 1982 (Box 239, Folder 8)
    - Teach for America, 2006-2008 (Box 239, Folder 9)
    - Title I, Elementary and Secondary Education Act of 1965, 1981-1982 (Box 239, Folder 10)
    - United Negro College Fund, 1985 (Box 239, Folder 11)
    - University Community Collaborative at Temple University, 2009 (Box 239, Folder 12)
    - Vocational education file, 1984-1985 (Box 239, Folder 13-14)
  - Foreign Affairs, 1977-2009; 6.
    The Foreign Affairs subseries includes mateials on international relations, the Middle East, and other related topics.
    - Afghanistan, 1988 (Box 240, Folder 1)
    - Afghanistan, 2009 (Box 240, Folder 2)
    - Africa, 1990 (Box 240, Folder 3)
    - African famine and drought, 1985 (Box 240, Folder 4-5)
    - Agency for International Development, 1989-1990 (Box 240, Folder 6-7)
    - Aid to former Soviet states, 1992 (Box 240, Folder 8)
    - Ambassadorial and senior foreign service nominations, 1998 (Box 240, Folder 9)
    - American Egyptian Jewish Delegation, 1997 (Box 240, Folder 10)
    - American Israel Public Affairs Committee, 1980 (Box 240, Folder 11)
    - American Jewish Committee, 1997 (Box 240, Folder 12)
    - Americans Schools and Hospitals Abroad, 1990-1992 (Box 240, Folder 13)
    - Amnesty International, 1987 (Box 240, Folder 14)
    - Andean Plan and anti-narcotics in Latin America, 1991 (Box 240, Folder 15)
    - Arab interest groups, 1985-1989 (Box 240, Folder 16)
    - Armenian genocide, 1986-1990 (Box 240, Folder 17)
    - Armenian/Turkish conflict, 1985 (Box 240, Folder 18)
    - Arms sale to Saudi Arabia, 1990 (Box 240, Folder 19)
    - Asia Foundation, 1986 (Box 240, Folder 20)
    - Asylum application standards report, 1987 (Box 240, Folder 21)
    - Automated export system, 1999 (Box 240, Folder 22)
    - Bahamas, Resolution of decertification, 1989 (Box 240, Folder 23)
    - Bahrain stinger missile transfer ban, 1987 (Box 240, Folder 24)
    - Baltic states, 1988 (Box 240, Folder 25)
    - Baltic states, Lithuania, 1990-1992 (Box 240, Folder 26)
    - Bosnia, 1993 (Box 240, Folder 27)
    - Bosnia, 1995 (Box 240, Folder 28)
    - Bosnia, Balkans, Specter statement, 1992 (Box 240, Folder 29)
    - Bosnian aid, 1998 (Box 240, Folder 30)
    - Burma, 2001 (Box 240, Folder 31)
    - Cambodia, 1985 (Box 240, Folder 32)
    - Canada, 1982 (Box 240, Folder 33)
    - Caribbean Basin, 1990 (Box 240, Folder 34)
    - Central America, 1983 (Box 240, Folder 35)
    - Central America, 1983 (Box 241, Folder 1)
    - Chile, 1984 (Box 241, Folder 2)
    - Chile, 1989 (Box 241, Folder 3)
    - China, 1981-1982 (Box 241, Folder 4-6)
    - China, 1985 (Box 241, Folder 7)
    - China, 1990 (Box 241, Folder 8-9)
    - China, 1999-2001 (Box 241, Folder 10)
    - China, CRS reports, 1996-1999 (Box 241, Folder 11-14)
    - Columbia, 1989 (Box 241, Folder 15)
    - Contact lists, 1978-1980 (Box 241, Folder 16)
    - Contra funding and expedited procedures, 1985-1986 (Box 241, Folder 17)
    - Council of Jewish Federations, 1988 (Box 241, Folder 18)
    - Cuba, 1990-1992 (Box 241, Folder 19)
    - Cuba, 1999 (Box 241, Folder 20)
    - Cuba, Liberty and Solidarity Act, 1995 (Box 241, Folder 21)
    - Cyprus-Turkey-Greece issue, 1988 (Box 241, Folder 22)
    - Diplomatic immunity legislation, 1987 (Box 241, Folder 23)
    - Directory of Chinese officials, National-level organizations, 1985 (Box 241, Folder 24)
    - Eastern Europe, 1990-1991 (Box 241, Folder 25)
    - Ecumenical Patriarch Bartholomew Bill, 1997 (Box 241, Folder 26)
    - Egypt, 1985 (Box 241, Folder 27)
    - Egypt, 1988 (Box 241, Folder 28)
    - Egypt, 1990 (Box 242, Folder 1)
    - El Salvador, 1981-1985 (Box 242, Folder 2-5)
    - El Salvador, 1990 (Box 242, Folder 6)
    - El Salvador, 1990-1991 (Box 242, Folder 7-12)
    - El Salvador, Extended voluntary departure, 1983-1984 (Box 242, Folder 13)
    - Ethiopia, 1984-1985 (Box 242, Folder 14)
    - Federation visits to D.C., 1998 (Box 242, Folder 15)
    - Filipino Christian arrests in Saudi Arabia, 1999 (Box 242, Folder 16)
    - Foreign agriculture, 1982 (Box 242, Folder 17)
    - Foreign Aid Bill, 1985 (Box 242, Folder 18)
    - Foreign aid certification, 1988 (Box 242, Folder 19)
    - Foreign Operations, 1992-1997 (Box 243, Folder 1-5)
    - Foreign Operations, Hearings, Herbert L. Beckington testimony, 1990 (Box 243, Folder 6)
    - Foreign Operations, Hearings, Gregory J. Newell testimony, 1985 (Box 243, Folder 7)
    - Foreign Operations, Hearings, Secretary Schultz testimony, 1988 (Box 243, Folder 8)
    - Foreign Operations, Legislation, 1984-1985 (Box 243, Folder 9)
    - Foreign Operations, Requests and letters, 2001 (Box 243, Folder 10-11)
    - Foreign Operations, Schedule, 1989 (Box 243, Folder 12)
    - Foreign Operations, Trade, 1985 (Box 243, Folder 13)
    - Foreign Operations, Wish lists, 1988 (Box 243, Folder 14)
    - Founding Fathers for the American Promenade in Israel, 1990-1992 (Box 243, Folder 15)
    - Genocide Convention, 1984 (Box 243, Folder 16)
    - Germany and Japan UN Security Council inclusion, 1993 (Box 243, Folder 17)
    - Global chemical weapons ban, Specter article, 1989 (Box 243, Folder 18)
    - Greece, 1985 (Box 243, Folder 19)
    - Greece, Turkey, and Cyprus, 1995 (Box 243, Folder 20)
    - Guarantee Reserve Fund, 1988 (Box 243, Folder 21)
    - Haiti, 1994 (Box 243, Folder 22)
    - Haiti, 1994 (Box 244, Folder 1-2)
    - Holocaust victim insurance claims issue, 1997-1998 (Box 244, Folder 3-4)
    - Hourmozi family refugee case, 2001 (Box 244, Folder 5)
    - Identification Friends or Foe codes and terrorism, 1989-1992 (Box 244, Folder 6)
    - Immigration protected status background and issues, 1999 (Box 244, Folder 7)
    - India, 1982 (Box 244, Folder 8)
    - India and Pakistan, 1995-1998 (Box 244, Folder 9)
    - Intelligence and foreign policy articles, 1990-1991 (Box 244, Folder 10)
    - International Conference on Population, 1985 (Box 244, Folder 11)
    - International kidnapping, 1985-1987 (Box 244, Folder 12)
    - IMF, Additional funding testimony and talking points, 1983 (Box 244, Folder 13-14)
    - International security assistance programs, 1985 (Box 244, Folder 15)
    - International security assistance programs, 1986 (Box 244, Folder 16)
    - International Tribunal for the Former Yugoslavia, 1997 (Box 244, Folder 17)
    - International Tribunal for the Prosecution of War Crimes in Former Yugoslavia, 1999 (Box 244, Folder 18)
    - Iran, 1999-2002 (Box 244, Folder 19)
    - Iran and Bosnia reports, 1996 (Box 244, Folder 20)
    - Iraq, 1998-2007 (Box 244, Folder 21)
    - Israel defense aid, 1990-1991 (Box 244, Folder 22)
    - Israel, Ehud-Barak, 1997-1999 (Box 244, Folder 23)
    - Israel, Elwyn Hospital, 1989 (Box 245, Folder 1)
    - Israel-Iraq relations, 1990 (Box 245, Folder 2)
    - Israel-US relations, 1990-1991 (Box 245, Folder 3)
    - Israeli attack on Iraqi nuclear reactor, 1981 (Box 245, Folder 4)
    - Israeli and Jewish issues, 1994 (Box 245, Folder 5)
    - Israeli missing-in-action soldiers, 1996 (Box 245, Folder 6)
    - Japan, 1982 (Box 245, Folder 7)
    - Jesuits in El Salvador, 1990-1992 (Box 245, Folder 8)
    - Jewish issues, 1993-1995 (Box 245, Folder 9)
    - Jordan, 1998 (Box 245, Folder 10)
    - Korea, 1994-1995 (Box 245, Folder 11)
    - Kuwaiti arms sales, 1988 (Box 245, Folder 12)
    - Kyrgyzstan, 1994 (Box 245, Folder 13)
    - Letter to Specter from Assad, 1993 (Box 245, Folder 14)
    - Liberia, 1990-1991 (Box 245, Folder 15)
    - Loian guarantees, 1991-1992 (Box 245, Folder 16)
    - Mexico, 1985 (Box 245, Folder 17)
    - Mexico City policy and international family planning, 1987 (Box 245, Folder 18)
    - Middle East, Israel-Egypt-Jordan, 1987 (Box 245, Folder 19)
    - Middle East, Speech and floor statement, 1989 (Box 245, Folder 20)
    - Middle Eastern Peace Conference, 1990-1991 (Box 245, Folder 21)
    - Multilateral Assistance Initiative, 1989 (Box 245, Folder 22)
    - Multilateral development banks, Justification for appropriations, 1985 (Box 245, Folder 23)
    - Multinational Brigade (East) operational overview, undated (Box 245, Folder 24)
    - Multinational force in Lebanon votes, 1983 (Box 245, Folder 25)
    - National Endowment for Democracy, 1999 (Box 245, Folder 26)
    - Nazi war criminal extradition, 1996-1997 (Box 245, Folder 27)
    - Nepal missionaries letter, 1998 (Box 245, Folder 28)
    - Nicaragua peace plan, 1987 (Box 245, Folder 29)
    - NATO expansion, 1998 (Box 245, Folder 30)
    - Organization of Islamic Cooperation (OIC), 1998 (Box 245, Folder 31)
    - OPEC, 2000 (Box 245, Folder 32)
    - Overseas Private Investment Corporation (OPIC), 1999 (Box 245, Folder 33)
    - Pakistan, 1983-1984 (Box 245, Folder 34)
    - Pakistan, 1987 (Box 245, Folder 35)
    - Palestinian Liberation Organization (PLO), 1997 (Box 245, Folder 36)
    - PLO, Yasser Arafat, 1986-1990 (Box 245, Folder 37-40)
    - PLO, Yasser Arafat, 1986-1990 (Box 246, Folder 1)
    - PLO, Yasser Arafat, 1989 (Box 246, Folder 2)
    - Panama Canal, 1999 (Box 246, Folder 3-4)
    - Panama sugar quota, 1989 (Box 246, Folder 5)
    - Peacekeeping operations, Presidential Decision Directive 25, 1994-1999 (Box 246, Folder 6)
    - Peru, 1999-2000 (Box 246, Folder 7)
    - Philippines, 1981-1982 (Box 246, Folder 8)
    - Philippines, 1985 (Box 246, Folder 9)
    - Poland, 1985 (Box 246, Folder 10)
    - Poland, 1989 (Box 246, Folder 11)
    - Polish nationals issues, 1984-1985 (Box 246, Folder 12)
    - Jonathan Pollard, 1998 (Box 246, Folder 13)
    - Presidential Advisory Commission on Holocaust Assets in United States, 1997-2000 (Box 246, Folder 14)
    - Presidential involvement in Middle East peace process background, 1990 (Box 246, Folder 15)
    - Public Law 480, Food program, 1984 (Box 246, Folder 16)
    - Puerto Rican Self Determination Act, 1998 (Box 246, Folder 17)
    - Religious persecution newsclips, 1998 (Box 246, Folder 18)
    - Religious violence in Egypt, 1997-1998 (Box 246, Folder 19)
    - Romania, 2001 (Box 246, Folder 20)
    - Russia, 1994 (Box 246, Folder 21)
    - Russia, 1998-1999 (Box 246, Folder 22)
    - Rwanda, 1999 (Box 246, Folder 23)